myshaadi.in 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers myshaadi.in, which shall be referred to as “we”, “us”, or “our” throughout this Privacy Policy. “You” as a user of myshaadi.in, accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

We are committed to protecting personal and financial information disclosed to us. In the course of providing wedding planning and other related services, we will collect certain information from you. The intent of this policy is to disclose our privacy practices with regard to such information. 

### Information You Give Us

We require information from you in order for you to be an account holder of myshaadi.in or to be an active member or vendor of myshaadi.in. When creating an account you will be required to provide your: 

\- Name   
\- email address   
\- contact phone number 

You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. 

### Use of Your Information

myshaadi.in is committed to protecting your privacy in regards to your personal and financial information. The information gathered by us is used to understand your needs and to provide you with better service. For example, the information we collected is used to: 

\- Improve our user features and products   
\- Update our database with user geographical information   
\- Send periodic emails to our users about promotional items, contests, special offers and announcements.  
\- Contact you for market research purposes 

We reserve the right to disclose to third parties information about general subscriber usage of myshaadi.in and any related services, including information gathered during your use of myshaadi.in. Any information disclosed will be in the form of aggregate data (such as overall patterns or demographic reports) that does not describe or identify any individual user. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we do not share, trade, sell or allow access of your personal information to any third parties. 

### Security

We have firewalls and other means, attempted to ensure the security and privacy of information disclosed by you. All sensitive personal and financial information is restricted and our employees have access to your information only to perform specific tasks. While we have in place reasonable electronic procedures that safeguard your information collected online, no system on the Internet is completely secure. As such, we encourage the use of discretion when browsing the Internet or when visiting any website, including myshaadi.in. 

### Links to Other Websites

We have affiliate links to many other online resources. While we do not share, trade, sell or allow access of your personal information to any third parties, we are not responsible for the practices employed by these affiliates or their websites linked to or from myshaadi.in nor the information or content contained on these third party websites. You should carefully review their privacy statements and other conditions of use and you agree you provide information or engage in transactions with these affiliates at your own risk. 

### Business Transfers

In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets. Such a transfer has minimal effects on your privacy and shall not be deemed a sale or transfer of your personal information. The information you submitted remains subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy as it exists at the time of such transfer. 

### Protection of myshaadi.in and Others:

We will release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of myshaadi.in, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

### Request of Information Held

You may request to receive any information that we have collected from you as stated by law. Please email us at privacy@myshaadi.in to receive this information. A small fee may be charged for this information. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may e-mail us at info@myshaadi.in. 

### Updates to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason without notice to you. However, if such a change will affect your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by e-mail of the relevant change. We will also post changes in our privacy statement 30 days prior to a change. You should periodically check to see if this Privacy Policy has changed. 

Privacy Policy Effective Date: October 9, 2009.
